It is absolutely true and it all started with and in Strängnäs.
This is the 35-year-old who is suspected to have acted as a kind of manager
to the Foxtrot network.
In an eavesdropped call, Rawa Majid refers to him as "Strängnäs".
No one touches Strängnäs.
Strängnäs is my area.
Strängnäs is thus both a city and a person.
It paves the way for confusion.
"Are you going on a weekend to Strängnäs? Are you sick in your head?"
"Well, to the gangster! Health."
The person Strängnäs is gang criminal with connections to the Foxtrot network
But shootings are not his thing.
This is a real monster.
He works with invoices.
As a specialist at the Swedish Crime Authority says:
"The checks were deficient. It was difficult to follow up on the efforts."
Perhaps the municipalities were tricked because Strängnäs had a well -plastered facade.
A few years ago they showed high ambitions
when they did a real star recruitment.
They hired the recognized skilled socio -economist Johanna Möller.
Yes, the Johanna Möller, the Arboga woman - she who is so child in love.
So Strängnäs on the board and the Arboga woman as manager:
Could it get worse?
Now the gang is starting to get into the healthcare system and start health centers
Warns the Swedish Crime Authority.